bigappled.com 2016-10-11

# Privacy Policy - Big Appled

This privacy statement covers the website BigAppled.com. Please read this statement carefully before proceeding to access BigAppled.com. Your use of BigAppled.com indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

**Information Collection**  
BigAppled.com is the sole owner of the information collected on the BigAppled.com. BigAppled.may collect information from our users at several different points on the BigAppled.com site.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of BigAppled.com, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. Commenters may register anonymously. However, if a third party complains that a comment breaches our Terms of Service (e.g. libels them), then in accordance with our Terms, we will make reasonable efforts to contact the commenter and alert them to the situation. If we are required to by law to disclose commenters’ contact information, we will attempt to contact commenters to give them the opportunity to respond to such requests. Please refer to our terms of use for more information.

**Mailing Lists**  
BigAppled.com may launch a mailing list for te website BigAppled.com, in order to provide subscribers with relevant information – breaking news, or weekly or daily round-ups, for example. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site. Most of the time, these will be content from the site in question, but we may occasionally send out an email from a third party sponsor. This does not represent an endorsement by BigAppled.com of any products advertised therein. It will clearly be marked as advertising: please check it out, as we hope you will feel that it is relevant to you. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, please do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Discussion Group and Cookies**  
In order to further enhance the user experience, BigAppled.com runs a commenting service on some or all of the BigAppled.com  Sites where users can discuss common topics of interest. Users have the option of signing up for this service, and to do so must submit information including a valid email address. BigAppled.com  uses this information to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use and to pick out topics of interest to discussion board users. BigAppled.com  will not pass this information to any other organization except in aggregate form. The discussion board service may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. We store a cookie on each user’s machine that contains a username and encrypted password. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use BigAppled.com  products or services that require you to “sign in,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, not all BigAppled.com  services require that you accept cookies.

**Third Party Links, Websites and Services**  
The Websites contain links to websites and content operated by third parties. Such links do not mean or imply that BigAppled.com endorses, recommends, sponsors, or otherwise has any affiliation or relationship with any third party, and no affiliation or relationship should be presumed. BigAppled.com does not control and is not responsible for any aspect of such websites and content.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers BigAppled.com uses log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Business Transactions**  
In the event BigAppled.com  goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, BigAppled.com  may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the BigAppled.com  Sites.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever BigAppled.com  changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact the editor of the BigAppled.com  site in question, or send an email to [info@bigappled.com](mailto:info@bigappled.com) or mail us at BigAppled.com at 21 West 22nd Street, Suite 709, NYC, New York, 10010

**Contest Rules**  
These Contest Rules apply to all websites provided by BigAppled.com  (“BigAppled.com”) and its licensees (each, a “BigAppled.com Site,” and together, the “BigAppled.com Sites”) and sets forth the rules, regulations, terms and conditions of all contests conducted by BigAppled.com on the BigAppled.com Sites (the “BigAppled.com Contest.”) By participating in any BigAppled.com Contest, you agree to be bound by and accept all provisions of these Contest Rules. BigAppled.com reserves the right to amend or alter the Contest Rules from time to time.

In order to participate in a BigAppled.com Contest, participants must be 18 years or older, and must live in the United States or the District of Columbia. Employees and officers of BigAppled.com or its affiliates are prohibited from participating in any BigAppled.com Contest.

Unless otherwise specified in the Contest Post, only one entry per person is permitted. Participants may withdraw from any BigAppled.com Contest at any time.

Unless otherwise specified in the Contest details (the “Contest Post,”) participation in a BigAppled.com Contest is free, except for postage (if entry submitted by mail) and any taxes that may be payable by a participant as a result of winning a prize.

The participant consents to the entry of their name and other personal information and authorizes BigAppled.com to use, reproduce or such information. All writings, photographs and/or other materials submitted to BigAppled.com in connection with a BigAppled.com Contest become the sole property of BigAppled.com upon transmission, and will not be returned to the participant. Such material may be copied, edited, distributed, retained or destroyed by BigAppled.com at the sole discretion of BigAppled.com. Participants shall not submit any material that is not original to the participant unless expressly indicated to the contrary. It is strictly prohibited to submit to BigAppled.com any material that violates the copyright, publicity/privacy rights or other intellectual property rights of a third party, or that is in breach of obscenity or other civil or criminal laws.

Entries may be made via the BigAppled.com Sites by clicking “submit” in the Contest Post, or by mail to the following address: BigAppled.com , 20 West 22nd Street, Suite 709, NYC, New York, 10010 and/or otherwise as specified in the Contest Post.

BigAppled.com is not liable in connection with entries that are lost, damaged, or delayed in transit or via Internet delivery.

In the event of a dispute, entries submitted via Internet will be deemed to have been made by the authorized account holder of the email address cited on the contest entry form on the dated of submission.

Any intentional attempt to damage any BigAppled.com Site or to undermine the legitimate operation of any BigAppled.com Contest may be in violation of civil and criminal laws.

Where winner(s) are to be selected on a random basis, BigAppled.com shall use an online random number generator or other neutral system for selection of an entry at random.

BigAppled.com will notify the winner(s) by email, which will be sent to the email address indicated on the contest entry form. In order to secure a prize, a winner must respond to such email within 48 hours of receipt. Failure timely to respond to the notification, or upon request, to submit a timely affidavit of eligibility, will result in disqualification. In the event of disqualification the prize shall be awarded to the next eligible participant.

Prizes are not transferable. BigAppled.com reserves the right to substitute any prize for a prize of equal value without notice to the participant. The participant shall accept delivery of the prize or substituted prize.

All winners of BigAppled.com Contests are solely responsible for compliance with all applicable federal, state and local taxes.
